Why are you being so mean?
You're making him cry Kacchan
If you keep on hurting him,  I'll stop you
myself.
[Hmph] You want to pretend to be a hero?
You don't stand a chance without a quirk,
Deku.
Here's the sad truth.
All men are not created equal.
When I was four years old, I learned that
some kids have more power than others.
But that won't hold me back.
If anything, it pushes me to do better.
" Izuku Midoriya "
"Tatooin station "
That's one huge supervillain!
The
first incident was in Ching Ching City.
An extraordinary child was born who
radiated light.
" Papa "
After that, reports of people with
superpowers popped up across the globe.
No one knew what was causing these quirks.
Before long, the supernatural became the
totally normal.
Dreams are reality.
The world became a superhuman
society, with about 80%
of the population possessing
some uncanny ability.
Our streets look like scenes from comic
books.
A city swirled with chaos and confusion.
A new profession dominated our collective
consciousness.
It was an age of heroes.
The Punching Hero!
I wish I had a quirk that made me super
strong.
Everyone, please stay back.
The area is far too dangerous.
Whoa, the rescue specialist backdrop is
here.
He'll make sure, okay?
This guy must be pretty desperate to go
full monster in the middle of the city.
You know what happened?
Just some amateur.
He stole someone's bag and then got
himself cornered.
A quirk like that and he's just a petty
thief.
I got held up.
Trains out.
Another villain.
I'm not sure when I'm going to make it
into the office.
A big
name for himself.
One look at that dopey grin and I know
what you are.
A fanboy.
Sort of.
Assault, robbery and illegal use of powers
during rush hour traffic.
You are the incarnation of evil.
This special move on Dream Man,
choice of the clergy.
The pre-emptive.
Finding.
Laccertain Prison.
Can you cut off?
Masha.
Piece of cake for the world's next hottest
hero.
Hi there everyone, I'm Mount Lady.
And you don't have to worry about this
bomb anymore.
Masha.
Wait, she's getting all the credit?
With the rise of superpowers came an
explosive increase in criminal activity.
While governments were stuck trying to
figure out how to reform laws with quirks
in mind, courageous people started performing
heroic acts to keep our cities safe.
Protecting us against villains who abused
their powers for evil.
With overwhelming public
support, heroes found in
official places peacekeepers
overseen by the government.
Those who performed the best were paid the
most and got all the fame and glory.
Their careers depended on their ability to
stay in the spotlight.
Gigantification, huh?
Well, she's definitely got the looks and
attitude to be a crowd favorite.
And her quirk is really showing,
but it'll be kind of hard for her to get
her on much in the city without damaging
lots of things.
That means she might not be very useful.
What's that, Bad Boy?
You take a notes over there?
Wanna be a hero too, huh?
Yes, more than anything.
" Episode 1 : lzuku M idoriya: Origin "
"Aldera Junior High "
So, as third-year students, it's time to
start thinking seriously about your
futures and what you want to do with your
lives.
I could pass out some career-aptitude
tests, but why bother?
No, you all want to go to the hero track.
Yes, yes, you've got
some very impressive
quirks, but no power
usage allowed in school.
Get a hold of yourselves.
Hey, teach.
Don't let me in with this bunch of losers.
I'm the real deal, but
these guys will be lucky
to end up a sidekick to
some busted de-lister.
" Katsuki Bakugo "
You think you're better than that,
Katsuki!
Let's go, I'll take you all on!
You've got impressive test results.
Maybe you will get into UA high.
He's gonna try for the national school.
That school has a 0.2% acceptance rate.
It's impossible to get into.
That's exactly why it's the only place
worthy of me.
I ache off the mock tests.
I'm the only one at this school who stands
a chance at getting in.
I'll end up more popular than all might
himself, and be the richest hero of all time.
People all across the world will know who
I am, and it all starts with UA high!
Oh, yeah, Midoriya.
Don't you want to go to UA, too?
Yeah,
you're kidding, right?
There's no way you're getting into the
hero course without a quirk.
Well, actually, they got rid of that rule.
I could be the first one.
Listen up, Deku.
You're even worse than the rest of these
damn rejects you quirkless wannabe.
You really think they'd let someone like
you in when they could have me?
No way, you've got it all wrong.
Really?
I'm not trying to compete against you.
You've got to believe me!
It's just that I've wanted to be a hero
since I was little.
I may not have a quirk, but I can still
try my hardest, can I?
You'd never be able to hang with the best
of the best.
You'd die in the exams!
Defenseless is Zuku!
The school's already crappy.
You really won't embarrass it more by
failing so hard.
Hey, get back here!
"The same city"
If someone stops that monster!
Yeah, I won!
Suckerless catches mine!
Dude, where are all the heroes?
We're here.
Normally, someone would swoop in right
away.
Maybe they're all still busy from that
scene this morning.
Remember when we didn't have to worry
about randos with quarts all the time?
Seriously, there's no stopping them.
Yes, there is.
You know why.
I am here!
Oh, yeah, we should go to karaoke tonight.
Yeah, let's go.
Man, that fight from this morning is all
over the news.
Better write some notes down before I
forget anything.
I don't know what you think you're doing,
Deku, but we're not done.
What you got?
His diary?
Huh?
" Hero Analysis for the Puture "
Don't tell me you're taking notes on how
to be a hero.
It's so pathetic!
He's delusional!
A real funny guy!
Just give it back!
That's so mean!
Most first-string heroes show potential
early on.
People look at them and just know they're
destined for greatness.
When I'm the only student from the
Skarbage Junior High to get into UA,
people will start talking about me like
that.
They'll realize I'm legit the next big
thing.
That's not ego talking.
I just know I'm good.
Ego!
There's a little word of advice,
nerd.
Don't even think of applying, or else.
That's just sad.
I thought you at least had some fight in
you.
He finally gets it.
He'll never be a hero.
Better to find out now instead of later,
I guess.
You know, if you really
want to be a hero that
badly, there actually
might be another way.
Just pray that you'll be born with a quirk
in your next life.
And take a swan dive off the roof of the
building.
Something wrong.
That idiot.
You can't go around telling people to kill
themselves.
What if I really jumped?
What would he do then?
My dreams have turned into fish food.
That's enough.
Give it back.
Damn it.
" Hero Analysis for the Puture "
Stupid jerk.
Mom, hurry!
Time!
Ready?
Fester, let's go!
Jeez, I think you've added 10,000 views to
this one yourself, Izuku.
I don't know why you like it.
I think it's scary.
The video I loved was an old one.
Disaster footage from a long time ago.
But more importantly, it was the debut of
the greatest hero the world has ever known.
Who is this?
The guys already take 100 people at least,
and it hasn't even been 10 minutes.
This is crazy!
I can't believe it!
Universe!
If one's idea like quirk, I'm gonna be a
hero just like him!
Sorry, kid.
It's not gonna happen.
Oh, dear.
So you really think there's something
wrong then?
Most of the other kindergartners in his
class have begun to show signs already.
My records say you're a fourth-generation
quirk user.
What powers do you and the boy's father
have?
Nothing too special.
I can float small objects towards me and
my husband breathes fire.
They're useful enough, I suppose.
Izuku should have already manifested one
of these quarks for a combination of both,
but after viewing his X-rays, I don't
think he's going to.
You see, when superpowers first began
appearing, there were many research
studies conducted, and doctors discovered
a link between the bones and a person's
foot in their likelihood of developing a
quirk.
People with powers have only one joint in
their pinky toes.
Their bodies have evolved into a more
streamlined version of the human form.
You can see here that
Izuku has two joints in his
pinky, like roughly 20% of
the population these days.
Based on the research
that's available, it's safe
to say your son isn't
going to develop a quirk.
There's always a smile on his face,
no matter how bad things get.
Even when things seem impossible,
he never gives up.
I can be a hero, too.
I'm sorry, Izuku.
I wish things were different.
Mom, that's not what I needed you to say.
Couldn't you see?
My world was crumbling.
There was only one thing I wanted to hear.
"Watch Your Head "
I made a decision that day.
No matter what anyone else thinks,
I have to believe in myself.
And I'll keep smiling, just like him.
Only
a perfect skin suit for me to hide in,
kid.
Don't worry, I'm just taking over your
body.
It'll be easier for both of us.
If you don't fight back, it'll only hurt
for a minute.
You'll feel better soon.
I can't breathe.
Grab all you want, my body's made of
fluid.
Thanks for the help.
You're a real hero to me.
I didn't know he was in this scene.
I gotta get out of here fast before he
tracks me down.
My body, get it weak.
This can't be the end.
So funny.
Have no fear, you're safe.
Is that all?
Hey!
Wake up!
Thought we lost you there!
It looks like you're moving around all
right.
Sorry about that back there.
I didn't mean to get you caught up in my
Justicing.
Usually I pay more attention to keeping
bystanders safe, but it turns out the
city's sewer system is pretty difficult to
navigate.
Anyway, you were a big help.
Thank you.
I've captured the evil doer.
But the most amazing hero in the entire
world.
Oh my, the real thing.
In the flesh.
Standing right in front of me.
He looks so much cooler in person.
Holy crap.
I gotta get an autograph.
I gotta plan around here somewhere.
Please sign my notebook.
He already did.
Thank you so much.
This will be an heirloom.
A family treasure fasted out for
generations to come.
Well, I've got to get this guy to the
police so they can take care of him.
Stay out of trouble.
See you around.
Wait.
You're leaving?
Already?
Pro heroes are constantly fighting time as
well as enemies.
He can't go yet.
There are still so many questions I have
to ask him.
Now stand back.
I'm taking off!
Thanks for your continued support!
Hey, hey, hey, what do you think you're
doing?
Oh, that's a good point.
I just have a lot of things I want to ask
you personally.
You're by all time the paper hero.
Oh my, please.
Okay, okay.
I get it.
Just keep your eyes and mouth shut.
No!
Oh, my whole life just flushed before my
eyes.
Not a very smart move.
Bang on the door for a while.
Someone will let you in.
Now, I have to go.
See you on the flip side.
Wait, not yet.
One second.
No, I don't have any time.
I have to know.
Sorry, kid.
It's not going to happen.
I'm sorry, Zuko.
I wish things were different.
The school's already crappy.
You really want to embarrass it more by
failing so hard.
Sometimes I do feel like I'm a failure.
Like there's no hope for me.
But even so, I'm not going to give up.
Ever.
Is it possible to become a hero,
even if I don't have a quirk?
I'm a normal kid without any powers.
Could I ever hope to be someone like you?
Meeting All Might was a dream come true.
A real miracle.
Standing in front of me was the hero I'd
idolized most of my life.
I didn't realize it at the
time, but that chance
encounter would change
the course of my future.
" Next time "
I am here for the next episode preview.
That goo villain is taking a boy hostage
and is running a muck in the town.
This isn't good, but what I can't use my
powers much longer or...
You're a pathetic fraud, All Might.
Next time, when it takes to be a hero,
we pose risk our lives for its duty to put
our quirk to the test and go beyond our
limits.
" Next time:What lt Takes to Be a Hero"
Plus, Ultra!